Hello,
hello. I
'll send you some pictures. I do
n't have any.
Kang Tae-gong, Manna-ri, hello.
Just a moment.
Hair. Even though I got an
aroma perm for my bangs, I
don't blow-dry them, so it's the same
thing every time. I had a cold last week, right? As for whether I'm completely cured, I don't think so.
Most of the symptoms have disappeared, but I
still feel like I have a cough every now and then. Nice to meet you.
I feel like I'm feeling better.
But somehow, my
energy level hasn't fully returned.
When I work out, I feel a
little weaker than before.
It's hard. I
lost a lot of weight because I succeeded in dieting for a cold. It
wasn't easy to gain weight. Anyway, I lost
muscle mass after
catching a cold and
when I felt a little better, I
went camping.
Those of you who have seen the pictures will have seen it, but we
went camping in the famous mountain in Gapyeong, and we
went to the ice valley. Yesterday, I
went there and came back, so I
think I worked out for the first time in a week. I
feel a little weak and not very energetic. I'll
recover. It
won't show up here. I
made a 1-minute video and
uploaded it.
Hello, unnie.
But this is something I
really wanted to do. This is
in the winter.  I
didn't want to do it alone. I
did it alone, but I had to be
prepared for when I do this with other people, so I would
n't be the first one out. I
did it as a rehearsal, but I
thought it would be harder to endure if I actually went in.
First of all, to go to a place like that, you
have to walk around while enduring a certain amount of snow.
Of course, there are other ways, but I
wore cross-shoes and went in, and
snow got inside my Crocs, so
it was colder than going into ice water.
My
French shoes were full of snow,
and the water I didn't drink mixed with my feet, and I kept showing
off, so
my feet were really
cold. How can I get in here in this condition and
actually wake up like this, my body isn't that cold,
like when I took a cold shower.
Of course, I didn't get to my destination, but it's
not that cold, but my body isn't
that cold.
My hands and
feet are cold. My hands are cold, but even so, there's no
way to hide them. Even if they're like that, my feet are still
in my pockets.
Next time I go, I'll have to get
my feet wet.  I thought there was a way to protect myself a little better. It
might be easy.
What about the clothes? I just brought them and put them
in a plastic bag. I
brought a swimsuit here specifically to go in.
This one
has a functional T-shirt, so I think I wear it a lot. I
brought a swimsuit. My
house is
near a campsite, so there's a lodging facility. I can sleep
there,
shower,
change, and
put my wet clothes in a plastic bag.
Hello, Curling. My
feet are really cold on the grass. It's really
snowing and I have rhinitis, so walking on the snow for even five minutes is just too much. My
feet just hurt so much. I kept
thinking, "I have to escape from here, I have to escape from here."
I recently
watched a documentary on YouTube, and it
talked about people living in the Himalayas. The
first thing I saw was the story of people
digging for Cordyceps sinensis in the Himalayas. It
seems they can only grow peach blossoms a certain number of times a year. But now, they dig them up
like a seasonal business
and sell them to China.
After the Nepalese people saw that, the algorithm recommended it,
and now
people living in Nepal
are trying to send their children to school.
To send them to school, they
have to cross a river in the middle because it's so far away.
But it
must not be easy to make a raft at an altitude of 5,000 meters.
Of course, since there's a forested area and the
trees don't grow,
how can you make a raft?
There's no way to cross the river normally, so you
can only go in the winter when it's frozen.
And that frozen road, I
think they called it "cha" or "chada" (crossing the road).
The name of the road is similar to the
Korean word "chada" (crossing the road). I'm a
little
skeptical, but they have to cross that "chada" (crossing the road). The
sun doesn't shine at night, and it
drops to -40 degrees Celsius at night. Even during
the day, it's -20 degrees Celsius in the shade.
But when the sun shines, it's right near the equator, right? I'm in the Himalayas, so it's cold because the altitude is high. That area, based on latitude, should be considered a tropical region at all times. Maybe that's why the sunlight is so strong.  When
the sun rises, the snow melts, but
the ice is high, so you have to leave early in the morning when the ice is completely frozen to be
able to cross
safely. However, if you only walk safely, you
won't be able to cross the river in time, so you
have to
cross when the ice isn't frozen or in a known place. So how do you walk? You just have to get wet and cross. People
have to send their kids to school, so some old man or grandfather-like
father of children has been
hit hard by the wind and waves, so he's
almost like a grandfather now.
There were some old men who looked like grandfathers, but they
didn't want their clothes to get wet, so they took off their pants, and since their
feet couldn't get hurt, they wore a pair of boots. The eel was
n't that high, so they put on their
boots when the water got in. They took off their pants and crossed while carrying all their belongings. Wow,
looking at that,
from my perspective as someone who actually experienced it, I just
went in for a bit, came out, and
went straight to a warm place. They
could
go indoors. Those people
said that they had to go from Maenggol to the Himalayas at an altitude of 5,000 meters for about a week. Even if you
go fast and your
feet get cold, it's
still the Himalayas.
Even if I succeeded in crossing the turmeric, even if I succeeded in crossing the river, it's winter, and even if I succeeded in crossing the persimmon, it's ice and snow, and I have to sleep there. This is the real difficulty of life, and my feet must be so cold, what should I do? Those thoughts are especially intense
from the perspective of someone who has experienced ice lips.
I think we live comfortably
living in Korea. They
say everything is relative, but it's
very
comfortable.
Hello, I
think I did it a long time ago. It was something that happened a
long time ago, and it was an algorithm.
So,
when there was a place to do something, honestly, it was
n't a big deal. It's
similar to taking a cold shower with bangs, but it's similar. It's just a
little more inconvenient to change clothes or something, but
since you don't have to stay in that state forever, it's
not that big of a deal. You can
do it. It didn't seem like a big
deal.
After that, you could
conveniently change clothes or take
off all your clothes and wait in the cold water in the winter and
do that.
But this is really very true. It's
reallygreat.
The body doesn't move well. When it's cold,
even if you're just exposed to the cold wind in the winter, the body is different.
It's
special and dry heat, and
moisture is
different from the outside and inside, and
things like cryotherapy.  It's minus
80 degrees, you know, but you go in there.
It's minus 80 degrees in a barrel,
honestly, it's not that cold.
But if
our bodies are exposed to minus 80 degree liquid
like that, we'll
freeze to death.
Similarly, we can survive for a very long time in places where it's minus 1 degree, or
even 0 degree, or even outside, but if you
go into cold water
like this and are exposed to 1 degree 0 water,
your skin
loses body heat incredibly quickly. It's
really
strong to wait and come out and snipe and stuff.
This place is really
no joke.
Anyway, it's
fun. Have
you tried it at least once? We need to
meet up just to do this, but we're going to Cheonggyesan Mountain
next Sunday. As
the company
said, I think we can only soak horses, so
soaking horses
isn't fun.
What should we do?
Russia. Even if we
don't go all the way to Russia, here is this place. This is a
place you can walk to nearby. We
did it here, but if you go a little further, it's
much deeper.
And one of the lessons we learned from that time is that there's
ice frozen like this here.
Here,
here, the ice is frozen like this. You
can break it with your feet and
this.  It doesn't break easily with bare hands, and
if you're going to break something and go in, you
should definitely break it thoroughly from the outside before
throwing more rocks. If there are
ice fragments scattered around while you're inside, you
might get scratched when you submerge and pull your body out. Other
than that, there wasn't much to do. Yes, you
asked what you needed, and you
just needed to be ready. The
channel is on hiatus, and there was an oil bath
experience. Is that okay? I
wonder. Do you
take a bath in oil? I wouldn't
really recommend it. There are
a lot of bad things in the school,
but you actually get into crude oil and bathe. I do
n't think many people would want to do that. Wow, just
thinking about it is terrifying. It's so
disgusting, but
I won't do it.
Of course, I don't recommend it. You
won't die, so I'll make you do it. You wo
n't die.
People who dig today
get hit with morning bombs all the time, and I haven't heard of anyone dying from it yet.
It's horrible.
At that time,
my mouth was talking. The
gasoline smells really bad,
and crude oil is
sloshing around. It
has all kinds of things in it, and it seems really horrible. But
that's what I did.
InStyle is
always there. The
original approach  Hello Wolf.
[Music]
Since last time, after asking a question, I heard that it's good to have more roosters when raising 6,
don't you worry about them fighting? 6.
When raising chickens for meat, it's
good to have more roosters because the hens
grow bigger. There's a significant difference in size over the same period of time.
So, the more roosters you have, the
more heads you can get.
But
even so, because we slaughter our broilers early,
before you start showing any fighting between the hens and the hens,
look. The hens have
to be around 4 months old, maybe 5 months old, when Song Seong-suk gets up, and
Hwang Seong-suk gets up, for
the hens to
become aggressive like thugs or chase them around freely.
Before that,
the hens and roosters are
the same, only the size difference and the appearance are a little different.
So you don't have to worry about fighting at that time. There's no
need to worry about roosters fighting more.
Chickens
will go and peck at anything that's injured or bleeding. That
doesn't matter if it's a hen or a rooster. If one of them is hurt or one of them is injured, they'll go home and eat it, so you
have to be careful. The
water went in.
It went in and came out quickly,
less than 20 seconds.  It'll work. The amount of time I've
been in today has
n't even been 20 minutes. Should I time it? I haven't been in yet. From the sitting position, the place where my feet are. If I think about it from this point on, I was the only one in at that time.
About 20 seconds.
Over 20 seconds. I
went in at 7:35:30.
Including about 32 seconds in the video, I was in for 35 seconds.
But it was dangerous and I
couldn't do anything because I was afraid it would break. It was
shallow and dangerous, so this place was ambiguous. I said I was
the only one doing it at the time, so I'm the only one.
But even if it's not that cold next Sunday, it
's not easy to walk around barefoot in this weather.
I walked on the snowy road a bit, and
my feet were really cold this time and last time. If you're
going to be a queen, it would
be good to go in cool.
Hello, that guy.
But this is really doable after trying it.
Only those who want to do it should gather separately and try getting
in the water once more.
What should I look for in Hypoi?
Why should I look for it? It
was a girl group. Nijins is
an old, old song.  I thought you were talking, but if you
turn it on too much, you'll get caught, so
if you get copyright infringement,
isn't it quite as harsh compared to a cold shower at home?
The water is colder, but it
's not like it's not cold just because you take it at home. The
biggest
difference compared to taking a shower at home is that at home, you just wipe off the water, dry
yourself with a towel, put on clothes, and you're done. But
here, you
can't wipe off the water and have to walk out.
Depending on where you are, the walk out
can be a bit rough. The
place I went in recently, the
way back up was a bit
rough. My
shins got a lot of scratches as I went in and out. Because it's
wild, the
human body is so weak that even a slight
brush doesn't tear everything apart.
That
depends on where you are, so you can
go get
it. If you go to the beach, that won't happen. And you
can't change clothes right away when you come out.
Actually, my body isn't that cold. What was the temperature that day? It
wasn't really that cold. It
was like 7 degrees in the morning,
but my feet are cold now. My
hands and feet.  I don't like it, but my hands
might not come in like this, and I could
prepare something like a hot pack and
hold it like this, and I
'd be able to report it somehow, but
r is the problem. There's
not really a way to warm them up right away, so outside, that's a bit
ambiguous.
And for my feet, like the rest of my body, I just go in and out of the water,
but my feet have to
go in and out again, and they're
exposed to one place for a much longer time, so it's
a bit cold. I think you
sent me a link, but it
doesn't work on YouTube.
I can't see it. Is
the game tolerable? It's so
cold that it doesn't seem easy to stay in for a long time. If
you go in with several people, it
might take longer, but when I compared the time earlier when I went in alone, it was just
35 seconds. It's
cold, but the cold actually
passes quickly. It doesn't
leave any aftereffects, so it
doesn't
feel like that. In fact, after about five minutes, I don't really know if I did it or not.
What's an oven? Just wipe it out with water and that's
it. You learned it. You
said there's not much to do there, but I hope you're
learning a little.
Anyway, getting into cold water is
n't as big of a deal as you think,
but it's still fun. The
idea itself is kind of funny, isn't
it?  I think it would be good to try it again.
These days, many people learn to dance on YouTube. There's
nothing they don't teach. There are videos
on YouTube showing how to play instruments like the violin. If you
have some talent
or basics, you
can do it.
Most black people
know
why singing is so difficult.
This year, I sang it.
That guy in Gimcheon who introduced me to a house introduced me to Adam. I'm
going to see him next week, the week after that.
If things go well, I
think we can avoid the media. I do
n't know where the hay was dried in the river.
In that case, they
didn't
use livestock. They just
slightly modified the gradual relationship and the terrain.
What's the improvement? As
I mentioned back then,
bringing compressed air into a desertified area and
feeding it raw grass
is Ellen Savery's method. It's
Holistic Management. The
method shown in the video I showed you back then is different.
Regenerative agriculture
doesn't refer to a single, fixed method. Quite a
few people are practicing regenerative agriculture without
using livestock.  There are also
some
things that actively utilize agriculture, such as
growing cover crops and using
them as green fertilizer even if they don't generate profits.
It's a type of regenerative agriculture. It's much healthier to grow
something than to do nothing or leave the land empty.
[Music]
But now, compared to the holistic approach of collecting management, which looks
at everything holistically and utilizes
all available resources and
such,
there are aspects of approaching things piecemeal, such as
using only cover crops.
In any case, what Saudi Arabia has done is
pour money into creating something.
Most of them
work with very poor people on huge tracts of land. In
Saudi Arabia, it's a project that
started with capital, so
English is different.
As for singing skills, I
always go to an Asian singing academy. I've been
wanting to learn singing lately. I
wondered how long I would have to live with dyslexia, and if
learning would help me improve, so I
went.
But when you go, the teacher always
needs to motivate you, or
Rather than motivation, I
need to keep cheering them on because I won't make money if I just give up.
Every time I go, they say I'm getting better and
getting better at a rapid pace. I
was worried because of the emperor.
Are you okay? I'm okay now. It
lasts quite a while after I take it. I think it lasts about 10 hours.
I
don't have it here. I recently bought a few supplements.
Four. I
bought taurine again, which I used to
take. I actually didn't see the effect of taurine, but I'm alone. There's a monk and my husband, so I haven't seen it. Even if I don't get it, I thought it might help. So I bought it again because it's foul. Then I bought creatine, inositol, and leucine. I bought it because I thought I'd take leucine between meals and exercise, but I
haven't had time to try it yet. I
tried leucine because I thought it might be a way to gain muscle a little faster while exercising. Creatine and taurine are
often used as supplements for exercising,
but I
heard that inositol is also very helpful for overall vitality and energy levels, so I bought it after seeing it.
Energy level  Not only that, but innercitol
helps muscles absorb glucose,
bones absorb calcium, and
other nutrients. It also
helps burn glycogen,
improves insulin sensitivity, and allows
us to exert explosive energy.
So, I
thought there was no reason not to try it.
Normally, it's
a nutrient that we can create from glucose, so it's not an essential nutrient. You don't have to take it, but I thought it might
be helpful to take it in addition, as a bit of a biohacking activity.
Drinking coffee, or
engaging in diuretic activities, or even alcohol, would be helpful.
Other activities
can impede absorption or
lead to waste and deficiency,
but as far as I
remember, I
don't do much of that. Of course, since I
drink a lot, it might be eliminated by the alcohol, but coffee,
like coffee, is
a two-track drug. It blocks absorption,
and then acts as a diuretic in the urine to prevent absorption.
Coffee
almost never does that.  I don't drink it,
so I don't think it's that bad,
but it seems to have the effect of making you feel warmer when you eat it,
so I thought I should
try it and bought it. The
other ingredients seem fine, so I don't think it matters,
but I
bought inositol in pure powder form and
only inositol in tablet form. The tablets contain various ingredients without any additives.
Rice flower contains the most, so
rice flour contains the most, so it
has a grainy smell from rice flour. I'm not
sure if that's the reason, but when I
take inositol, I get restless pain. My
fingers and toes hurt so much. This
isn't the only time it happened. I tried it once and thought, "What's going on?" I
tried it again the next day after taking inositol, and it happened again. I'm
almost certain. I get really strange joint pain. My toes and fingers hurt. My other joints are fine. My knees, shoulders, and back are fine, but my toes and fingers hurt in a strange way, like I have rheumatoid arthritis. So I stopped taking it for the time being. It's
theoretically a good nutritional
supplement,
and I looked it up, but I couldn't find
any side effects or anything.  There isn't. I
can't even tell why my fingers hurt, but they still hurt.
So I don't know what to do.
[Music] I have
n't really talked about anything else. I've never done anything. I just
sing and
take singing lessons.
It didn't help when I took taurine because of my cold, but it did
n't work. Now, actually, did I start taking it yesterday? Or the day before yesterday? I think I started taking a few, but I still don't have the strength, maybe because of my cold. A
few days ago, I
was putting stickers on a children's quiz on the street, and
the answer was, "
What kind of animal would be needed in a difficult region of Africa for pigs and goats?" I got them all right
in a row.
It's a red goat vibe, so
goats are good. Chickens and pigs need to be
fed grain, so we
need to raise a lot of animals that eat grass that we can't use.
But
sending just goats
isn't the end. We
can do that holistically management together now.
Or maybe donating money to Savory Herbs would
be better. Just send it here. It
won't be difficult because there's a shortage of
goats. I don't know how to manage the goats,
that's the problem. Just sending it here makes me
happy. I
don't need to eat less than when I cook. I'm just
eating,
right?
When I drink Campbell's coffee.  If it's transmitted, it's
all transmitted.
In the end, when you
drink something, you always
burn it and drink it.
How much oxygen did you consume? I
didn't eat carbohydrates directly. I
often baked sourdough bread, so I
ate bread often, and I hadn't eaten fruit for a few days, but
after a long time,
what's the name of it? I eat
rice once in a while, and a little other fruit. When I eat bread, I put some honey on it. Yes, sometimes maple syrup. I don't eat that much, but I don't eat that little either. It's the situation. They say it's not GMO rice flour, but I
don't know why, but it hurts when I eat it. Ca
n't you still eat the plus series? I
haven't tested it recently, but I do
n't really want to. I'm an
athlete, so I don't
eat little. I don't eat a lot, but I
think I eat it consistently. Is
Himalayan pink salt the worst?
Compared to domestic sea salt,
it's not. There
's a rumor that Binggeu Salt mixes it with bricks and sells it. I've
never looked into that.
On the other hand, to be
honest,
from the perspective of a pink salt mining community,
I wonder if there's any difference between a rock and salt. There must
already be a lot of salt, so
why would they bother mixing it with bricks in that vast, endless salty mountain?
Even if it actually existed, I do
n't think it would be much. This is purely a brain teaser, so I don't think it's worth using, and since it's not related to anything, I don't know for sure, but I still don't think there's a problem. I almost never eat it. Sometimes I
eat it like this at home,
but I don't eat it unless absolutely necessary.
The reaction varies quite a bit depending on the type.
Butfor now, if you
compare it to LM, it's good,
not bad.
Of course, since it's
salt with almost no
anhydride, the amount of magnesium is low.
The amount of magnesium in salt is directly related to the amount of brine in the salt.
That's why
it and salt are high in magnesium.
In Korea, salt without brine,
sea salt without brine,
has a lot of magnesium.
Do you know your diet secret?
What kind of diet are you talking about?
But when I
ask you this question, my heart
aches.
Where should I start? If you
ask me
out of the blue what your diet secret is, it seems like you have some kind of universal secret, right?
That's the kind of question.  If it exists,
dieting isn't like clearing a game quest
or
having a set strategy that
can cover everything. The
very idea of ​​a "law" makes no sense.
Everyone's situation is different, their
base is different, and their starting point is different. If you suddenly
ask them how to lose weight, it's
hard to cook. I
saw on their profile that they were a heavy smoker,
but after a while, they
changed to a "moderate smoker." That's
their nickname.
At first, they lose weight well, but then they start eating a lot of
processed foods and
vegetables, and their
telescope breaks down and they can't lose weight.
Teacher Yang says that there are a lot of
stories on keto cafes about people who lose weight but then can't lose it again.
At first, they lose weight well, but when they go
back to eating a regular diet, they
don't lose it this time. When
those people
lose weight on the ketogenic diet, they
eat all kinds of processed foods and vegetable bombs and
throw away all their intestines.
So far, they've been successful.
Does that mean it's not easy to lose weight?
Mr. Magicman, you weren't low on carbohydrates to begin with. Is it
because of that stress that you
don't go to Cheonggyesan?
This is fun. Smoking is
really fun.  You said you
enjoyed life by spreading
it out, so when you came out of Cheonggyesan Mountain, you should
go get some cold water instead of Cheonggyesan. Once you get some, the world
becomes more fun. Oh, you
didn't eat it and then you ate it in December. I don't think you used to eat it, so when was the last time we met? Anyway, I was surprised that you did
n't eat rice when you went to Tapgol Sundae. You said you didn't eat rice there, but there was so much meat that you didn't need to. Anyway, you didn't eat rice at a noodle
restaurant?
Hello, hyung.
Losing weight by eating white rice
is something that can happen these days, but it's
not like eating on your period is a secret to dieting.
Hello, Magari. Do
you know those who say they don't lose weight even if they fast?
Those who say they
don't lose weight even if they fast. It's a bit
unusual. In fact,
I wonder how I don't lose weight when
I fast, but my body is amazing. It's because the body has fat cells that absolutely hold onto all the fat and never give it up. I have no energy at all, and I think I'd rather
starve to death than lose weight, but
it's not normal.
That's right. It's
not a lie that won't go away. Some
people say no, but I'm
not sure how much you did.
Hello, I just
had a delicious American sirloin roasted in butter.
Can I eat all the remaining fat? It's
a waste to throw away the fat. Do you
wash the meat to eat the fat as soon as you fold it? The deficit starts right from the moment you fold it. They tell you to eat this as the main ingredient, and since you don't eat the fat separately by eating 300g of meat, you'll
reduce the calories a lot, so if you eat like this, you'll
lose weight. That's true, but I'm
not sure if Professor Yang tells all his patients like this. As far as I know, if you
don't have much weight to lose but want to talk to
Professor Yang, he
tells you to eat less and reduce calories, like 500 calories a day. It's
similar to that. It
gradually increases,
but if you
eat a meal and then go for a walk, is that right?
Or how many minutes does it
take? If you eat, wash, and exercise, it's better to wash and do it right away all day. You don't have to wait. Hello, Jeongwon. I clean the plate clean, but if I just eat spears, I get dizzy. Are you doing this repeatedly?  Is
that because you eat a lot of it?
Daechang has a lot of
fat, right? Even if I eat just a little, I get dizzy. Are there any strange
symptoms without eating it? I don't
feel well because I don't eat much. It
's ambiguous. And I
sleep a lot at night.
But I'm not sure about this. Is it because I do
n't wash my clothes and sleep, so I
need more sleep,
or is it because the leaves can't sleep?
But it seems like it's not just me. Is
it because I still don't close the blinds and it's bright, or is it because I'm exposed to a lot of blue rice before going to bed? There are so many changes, it's hard for me to pinpoint one. I don't know if it's because I don't wash my clothes while I sleep, but I
think I sleep a lot lately. If I
don't set an alarm and go to bed, I
keep sleeping.
Before, my eyes would just open wide, but
when the time comes,
I keep sleeping.
Before, I used to spend
almost 9 hours a day,
9 hours or more. If I
was indoors and
had a room, I would
always wash my clothes. It's time to read only what I know, and if I'm in my room for more than 3 hours, I'd do half the work a day.
Maybe that's why I
wash all my clothes, but there
's not much static electricity.  The
best way is to
change the material of our clothes.
Natural materials like cashmere
are much less irritating than synthetic materials like polyester or nylon. Let's wear
clothes made of natural materials.
Every time we walk, we're busy, and we
eat a lot. So, when we're
in a state of being grounded, static electricity often builds up.
So, it escapes to
the ground. Just like when
lightning strikes,
lightning rods
send lightning to the ground.
What time does it last? Surely you'll sleep your whole life,
so that's how it is. But if you buy too much unnecessarily, the
machine is no joke. I
need to do more singles. Starting tomorrow, I'll work
hard in Washington.
Hello.
Then, it's a ring that doesn't let you lose weight. In
fact, I almost quit, but sometimes it
affects me.
[Music]
But if
there's no inflammation in the body, you
lose weight even if you don't eat
white rice. Rather than losing weight by eating white rice, I think it's because it's
healthy, so you can go to a healthy weight no matter what you eat.
When there's no inflammation in the body, in
other words, when the body is healthy, if you
don't eat white rice, you'll definitely gain weight
or not lose weight. It doesn't make sense. The
history of eating rice is short, and
not all people on Earth have eaten rice.  I didn't eat that. Saying that
white rice is an essential food is,
of course, nonsense. Wouldn't it be okay to just
eat white rice
?
When mold or other harmful bacteria are infesting your stomach or body, simply
cutting out raw vegetables won't solve the problem.
Even if you cut out all vegetables,
diet alone
might not be enough. They
could be from the environment.
Even if you don't let them in your room,
a child who's already grown might not have a strong enough
immune system to get rid of them.
Various internal interventions might be necessary.
Kimchi could also have an effect. Since it
contains red pepper powder,
if you're particularly sensitive to leptin in kimchi, red pepper powder, or red pepper powder, even a small amount
can cause you to develop symptoms as the number of times you catch them increases.
That's right, I didn't see it, so the
harm has been greatly reduced. It
creates static electricity.
That's how it is. Will it be
less?
Hello, I'm a
regular nerd. I actually have severe insomnia. Are
there any other nutritional supplements that would help?
3-in-1 B1 Megadus is the most common. It's
like allithiamine in the form of CFD.
When doing altitudinal megadus, you
should always make sure to take magnesium.
In that sense,
if I can't consistently take magnesium because I'm taking concentrates like Mag, I should
take a separate supplement. If I
take it separately,
something like glycinate would be good to have the threonate that goes straight to the brain.
I tanned with an old man. I came into a bare power plant. Oh, you
did well.
Why do I feel nauseous when I eat a discount? Take it
with a meal.
First of all, I don't think it's good to take it on an empty stomach.
With a meal.
This is just my opinion.
Of course, it
could change when you biowalk, but the original purpose
was different. Generally
speaking, it's a very
strange state to take nutrients alone.
Of course, nutrients come from food,
so I
think it's natural for them to be absorbed with meals.
In that sense, it's
better to take it with this rather than supplementing. This wo
n't apply to all situations.
Depending on what nutrients you're taking and why, it might be easier to take them on an empty stomach.
Anyway,
Taking it with meals generally has
fewer side effects, and I do
n't know why I feel nauseous even though I take it with meals. I don't know. I
don't know why I get joint pain when I take Inercito. I don't
know. I'm still
washing my face, but it's cold. You're
really working hard. Wow, you're really
amazing. If
you eat carbohydrates, you gain weight, and if you only eat meat, you
lose weight easily, which is not good for your body.
Rather than insulin resistance, if your
body is
n't 100% healthy in metabolizing insulin and blood sugar and such,
when you eat carbohydrates, your
blood sugar rises quickly, insulin is
secreted a lot,
blood sugar doesn't fall well, and so
on, then
when you drink carbonated beverages, you lose
weight very slowly or your body
becomes more prone to gaining weight. If you only eat this and
minimize insulin requirements, you
lose weight better, and that's possible.
If you wash your face with socks on, you
won't wash your face unless your socks are completely soaked. If
you eat milk, it's
not easy to repeat it, and it's not easy to eat a lot with the egg method.
Eating a lot is really
taking away. I'm only eating two meals these days, and
especially eating while drinking milk separately.
It's not easy.
I
eat a lot of different things these days, so it's hard to say I eat just one thing. I
consistently eat bone broth. I eat
meat, cheese,
butter, and
eggs.
Oh, and recently, I've been
eating the suttaeji that I raised a lot. Did our
ancestors swim while wearing straw sandals? Gypsies
can't be earthed.
Dead plants
can't be washed.
Only living plants with roots can be earthed. It's
hard to eat a lot of them with rain. It's easier to eat young ones, and it's
harder to eat a lot of young ones.
Now,
are you seeing any effects from 10 eggs? Yes, you always say that doing something seems good, but is there such a thing? Is there a level to something that's good? Brother, you eat so many good things that it's hard to categorize and talk about them one by one. You said that Ryusin is definitely effective.
I don't really know why Ryusin is effective. All I
know from Ryusin is that
taking about 2.6g causes muscle protein synthesis.
I don't know much about Lysine, which improves performance in strength training. Anyway, you
said it seems to be effective.  You
said inositol seems to be effective, and I
think Taehoon mentioned Tauri specifically, but is
[ __ ] effective?
When I have a cold, I can sleep almost all
day, although I wake up briefly. Do you
know what the original reason is?
Usually, I want to sleep more, but sometimes I can't. When
I'm sick, I
sleep a lot. I
think it's because my body is trying to recover while I sleep.
Rather than using energy elsewhere, I think the
energy used for training and other miscellaneous activities is used to
repair my body. I think you'll
do all kinds of treatments to this extent, but the
best are oysters, and
eggs aren't that great.
Creatine is good for weight gain and just
the feeling of losing some weight. I
don't know about the rest, but oysters are the top priority,
followed by lysine. Do you
eat a lot of oysters these days? Do you have copper there, too? Mokpo is also
full of oysters in the Namhae area. Looking at the oysters that are a staple for Koreans these days, it's a natural mountain valley. Not just anyone can go to the mudflats. Only one person per household registered with the fishing industry can
come out and turn on the
water.
He
used to pick up eggs from the ground like this with something like a king crab. He
uploaded the results of eating eggs for 30 days on his channel. As a
result, his muscles increased. He couldn't
eat them raw because of a white protein allergy, so
his stomach hurt too much. I saw that too. His
muscles did increase,
but it
wasn't like he was on steroids.
But it was a little ambiguous because
his Celsius calories increased significantly.
For example, if you
eat similar calories but
only eat red meat instead of eggs, you would
have continued to exercise consistently. He had
n't been exercising,
and
to eat those eggs,
he also ate other things. He wasn't
just eating eggs, he was eating eggs. I
thought that if he had eaten like that, wouldn't other foods have had the same effect?
When I saw the growth or weight gain in the video,
however, he
kept talking about how energetic he was. He said that he needed to
sleep less and his
energy level was so high that he
felt like he had to keep doing something, so he
did a lot of things he hadn't done before. We
used to do a lot of things, and
it was a little harsh.
And if you eat them raw,
because of the avidin, I think I would have gotten better.  It hurt, that's
what they said.
In the protein society,
how many grams do I consume in a day? Right now, I
eat two 2g teaspoons, and I
consume about 4g. I
think it's difficult to meet the necessary effects if I focus on intermittent fasting.
What do you think about the effects of autophagy?
While fasting, if you
eat enough during meal times, you
can consume all these nutrients.
Butnow that you've
eaten only a little and are full,
it won't be easy. Of
course, eating is also a form of
training.
And I think
intermittent fasting every day
is enough for water phagy.
Because of autophagy, I do
n't think I'll miss out on doing it often, like 3 days a week. I
can do it once in a while.
Long-term methods, like 10 days a week,
seem to be similar, but I
think I'll only do it for 2 or 3 days.
Creatine is effective when I exercise for a long time.
So, I haven't heard of it even if I keep turning it over.
Megama is an alliteration, and
alliteration is a
supplement in the form of vitamin B1 TTFT.
Now, you
can take alliteration on its own, or you can take
vitamin B1 like alliteration.  When doing megadoses, you
need to take additional magnesium.
So, it would be good to supplement with magnesium glycinate,
MegaMag Percentage
Magnesium Threonate,
etc.
This is what I was talking about.
It seems to be effective for high-repetition training of more than 20 reps per set. You're
eating more than 100g a day. It
's really expensive.
Oysters are so expensive. I'll
eat a lot tomorrow. I'll eat
oysters first. It feels different whether I eat them or not.
Do you also
separate the egg whites when you shampoo?
It's been a while since I've used
egg yolk shampoo. I only used the yolk when I first started, and since
then, I've just kept it and
used water.
How about using the one from Transient Research instead of September?
Tris Mineral products are not allowed. First of all,
taking zinc separately is a bit ridiculous. I do
n't think we're gaining strength just because of iron. If we
eat a lot of meat,
there's already a lot of zinc in it. I do
n't think the zinc is the reason why oysters are effective.
Water is also rich in copper in addition to iron.
We
have a lot of zinc, so I don't think it's effective because of zinc.  It
makes no sense to take only iron as a supplement and feel like you're replacing water without taking any supplements that have a hydrating effect.  It does
n't just contain that. It contains all kinds of nutrients.
Instead, try taking it separately and then
increasing the amount with a meal to see how it is. Try
taking it separately and with a
meal. Don't just eat it on your own.
Okay. Instead, I have
n't taken it separately, but I'll try taking it with a meal.
Hanaro Mart sells medicine
with the same name as Bacchus, including taurine.
Is it effective?
Of course it is. Since it contains a towel, they
'll sell it as taurine. It's
much cheaper and better to just buy taurine separately and take it. Can I
take it here? What's my
raw meat? People who don't eat a lot of it say that
powder also has a negative effect. Do you
know why that is?
People who don't eat a lot of it do
n't recommend
all supplements when they have longevity. They say that all supplements
worsen intestinal diseases or delay recovery from intestinal diseases.
Personally, I
wonder if all supplements are related. I wonder if it doesn't have anything to do with specific cancers or not. I don't know the
exact reason, but since they
say it slows down recovery from intestinal diseases when they test, I guess that's just how it is. Hello
Vivian. I don't
really like protein powders except for SIM.
But you're
taking things like creatine and towels,
right? They're
all unnecessary, right?
Right? In principle, if you
consider school and unnecessary, it's
correct that you didn't do them.
But things like guards
seem necessary. C
might also be necessary. If we were to
just do 100% carnivore insurance, we would
n't be forcing animals into a state of shock and beating them like we used to. And
these days, minerals are so deficient, so I
think it's different from the past.
And some people may need it because their previous deficiencies were
severe.
What's the reason for taking
protein powder separately? But it's
a bit ambiguous to consider Yushin as protein powder.
Generally, protein powder
is extracted, like
yucheon protein,
pea protein, egg
protein, egg white protein,
etc. But the Yushin powder we're talking about here
feels a bit different. You're
taking a specific amino acid, and each
amino acid
has different effects on the body. For example, Lishi
stimulates muscle protein synthesis when taken in amounts exceeding 2.6g.
This was done before, but now it's gone.
2.6g is the maximum.
Generally speaking,
to achieve that level of energy, you'd need to
eat, say, 100g of cheese, or about
150g of lean meat. But
without eating that much, you can use leucine as a biohacking tool to
give the impression of eating more frequently.
Creatine, for example,
contains about 1g per 500g of meat.
So, you
can consume 1g by eating about 500g of lean meat.
Research has shown that 5g of creatine per day
is the ideal dosage.
When depression strikes,
it's efficient and can be
used to maximize efficiency.
To achieve that 5g of energy through food, you'd need to eat 2.5kg of meat per day.
Since 2.5kg is difficult, you
could try eating, say, 1kg of meat per day and supplementing the rest. For example, if you
exercise
unusually heavily, you could also try
taurine.  Even the same thing,
when I take a mega dose, there are
various effects like this. There are effects that
can only be obtained with megadoses.
Certain nutrients,
such as some vitamins, have
effects that don't really appear in regular doses, but are only effective with
megadoses. So, there are cases where people take
them in a way that
is not natural but rather a
bit biohacking or pharmaceutical.
If so, I've
seen many cases where it is effective for people with diarrhea. Can
you tell me how to extract only the cream?
Why does the cream float when you leave unchecked milk? It should float like this.
Do you need more vitamin C when you eat foods high in histamine? I don't remember clearly. It's
possible. To detoxify
histamine, we need
histamine enzymes, and vitamin C is needed to make histamine-decomposing enzymes.
So, it could be necessary in noodles. You
could say it's because it's hard to eat a lot of it.
But
meat and leucine can't be equivalent on a one-to-one basis.
Of course, meat
contains all the niacins,
most of the
minerals and B vitamins we need, and
various peptides.
Wishin is literally
just one amino acid among many sequestrants. It
doesn't contain any minerals or vitamins.
Yushin is just made in a lab.
Instead, is there a video explaining
why you should eat Mishin? There is no separate video explaining why you should eat Mishin.
There is a brief article about Yushin. It
briefly differs from the blog post about protein intake about lysine.
Add liver. You have
to eat liver.
When you scoop the cream that floats on top, is
it okay
if there is a little skim milk underneath? If you leave it at room temperature for a long time, the
three layers of Yulim curd whey will separate? When you say skim
milk is added to the bottom, are
you saying that it is okay to put low-fat milk that was separated from the cream when scooping it?
If you leave the milk in the petition,
don't you make the second and third layers of the picture card?
Quad and whey
don't separate into layers like that. You
also have to filter the request.
The cream is lighter, so it floats on top. Sometimes, the
quad and request are mixed, and the
layers are not clearly divided like this,
where the quad ends
and the request ends.  I
love the place where Misin is Kim Young-shin. Oh, that local person
made something like a name compatibility app. Is
this really an app? Please
upload that. If
you want to try it, try it. If you
put your name in, it will automatically
harden and show you the percentage. Are you
still taking vitamin K4 only in liquid form? I do
n't take any supplements these days. Ca
n't it work yet? Why? If
arteriosclerosis has already progressed, you
should be thorough in your diet. The doctor
says to take it.
Of course, you
should be thorough. The
only cases where statins are effective are if you are
over 50 or 60 years old,
male, and have had a
heart attack. It's meaningless unless you
have had a heart attack and are a man with a family history
or higher. It has
never been proven to be effective.
In other cases, statins are
meaningless. What is t? I don't
know if it's
newer, but for now,
rather than taking it carelessly, it would
be good to see a doctor other than your doctor.
Not all doctors recommend statins. It's a
great feature. Hello, Sinabro.
It's a great feature.  What?
Sugar consumption causes violence.
Well, I don't think so.
Eating a lot of it
doesn't seem to cause violence. Is
n't this rotten?
It's possible that a toothache from 2 could cause violence.
Hello, Alan.
How about taking Kate MK4 Worker Cover Naemi Oil? You'd
have to take a lot of Meoa. If you want to
take K2 with that, it might
not be economical. Even
10 micrograms would
be a lot.
Unless you're using MOE like we use lamb's fat and mutton's fat, and you're
using it as cooking oil, it's
hard to take a lot. It's
very difficult to read because I took a few pills as a supplement.
Trying megadoses of K2 or something like that
could help with arteriosclerosis. It will
prevent further progression as much as possible. You
need to take all the
vitamins and local vitamins. I think a deficiency of spiritual vitamins and
fat-soluble vitamins
is the biggest factor.
Do you brush your teeth with oil? Just water. The
product itself is
fine. I
know that Soryongtang and Frog are good.  Is
n't seolleongtang made
of earthworms? Is it because frogs and earthworms have something in
common? I wonder if
there aren't many places that raise earthworms cleanly these days.
Doesn't hiking provide earthing? Does your left foot have a earthing effect? ​​The
basic concept of washing is to ground yourself with the Earth.
In that sense, the
best place to raise earthworms is through your skin. However,
hiking boots
have soles all over the body,
or similar synthetic fibers that do
n't become viscous are attached, so
grounding through the soles of your feet isn't possible.
Even so,
the Earth is so vast that I think just
being in nature provides a de facto earthing
effect. If you
measure the voltage, it
drops to its lowest point even with shoes on. If you're outside, if you
're in nature, it's more
effective to have everything.
Even if you upload the link,
YouTube will automatically cut it off. If you
sweat a lot, you can
expel various toxins through sweat.
When raising edible earthworms,
don't you raise them cleanly? I
raise edible pigs.  I went to see it, but it was
n't growing cleanly.
It's a sudden Earthquake.
Look at the Earthquake. Are
there electromagnetic waves from the wind from a hair dryer?
There aren't electromagnetic waves from the wind, but in a
moment, electromagnetic waves will spread out in all
directions. Since you're sitting crooked, you must be working hard. Your shoulders look broad. I was working hard, but I got sick for the past week or so, and I couldn't do it because I went somewhere. I was working hard. My shoulders haven't widened, but they've definitely widened compared to the past. Yeonsan
is an autoimmune disease.
Could eating one or two raw peppers with a few meals for 10 years cause it?
There are other causes, but the
timing is the most important part. It's
often one of the autoimmune diseases. I do
n't know if all psoriasis is working immune, but
if most psoriasis is autoimmune,
eating one or two raw peppers with a meal
can have an effect. I've
seen enough, so you don't have to
date. I
don't know how far you've watched the Earthquake, but
dating isn't important there. Dating is
important, but it's not just for the savior.
People in relationships there do it because they
have to survive.
I'm talking about the Earth War, a Naver web novel, or
web novel,
but it's a bit weird to say it's only web novels,
but anyway,
there's a fantasy novel that left the deepest impression on me.
I
told you to read it,
and while
giving an economics
lecture, I said, "Of course, there are unmarried protagonists in non-married novels these days, but
marriage is more common.
How much effort did our ancestors put into having people born in the countryside? Why are you just cutting off that line?"
That's true. I
used to not sympathize with that kind of talk, but my
thoughts changed a little after my grandfather passed away. While I was caring for my grandfather after he passed away, I just
thought, "Ah,
I'm here as a nurse, and I'm the legacy
of my grandfather who is lying sick here right now. My
grandfather worked hard all his life,
lived hard,
raised his children, and those children worked hard,
and I was born. If
I were to
cut off that legacy, I
would feel bad for my grandfather. People
say that if you
eat BHC Hot Crispy Chicken, you'll
100% get a stomachache and stomachache,
but most people don't
take it seriously and say it's delicious. I eat it the next day on my day off.
He said he eats.
Oh, is that all? Even ordinary people
get stomachaches.
Do you like fantasy novels? I like fantasy. I don't
know much about martial arts novels. Oh, you don't know much about martial arts? You must
be a fake man. That wo
n't work.
Hello, Kang Se-in. This is
serious. If I want to
graduate from university, I have to read 5 martial arts novels.
But that long wind
is kind of an iconic word. If you trade, you
shoot a long wind,
and if you're a master of the Wugong, you shoot a long wind. But in actual martial arts novels, long winds
aren't used much.
Except in really rare cases, they rarely
shoot long winds. Sometimes they release tension, but they shoot a little bit of energy wave. It's like an energy wave,
but it's
not very common to blow wind.
That thought suddenly occurred to me. If I
eat a clean, traditional diet the day before, my stomach feels
good, but if I eat carbohydrates as a reward for dinner, I suddenly can't digest them. Why is that? It seems like you know exactly why you just mentioned. It's to prevent the carbohydrates that you eat as a reward for dinner from being digested. I
don't know what you eat, but it
seems like you know exactly why. How
many years have you been providing milk?
Generally, factory-farmed cows
don't often give birth three times. If they give birth twice or three times, they're
all gone.  It's a culling. The
3-mountain, 2-mountain thing
refers to whether two or three offspring were born.
Threats and samurai aren't generally related. It's
not that samurai in medical novels don't appear,
but they do appear in very minor ways. Here, the Haenam faction occasionally fought with Japanese kids, and that's about it. It's just that kind of
news that we hear about, like
media swords and telekinesis. Even if you
say Bokbunja wine,
you ca
n't drink much on
your own, right? It
probably won't be a lot, Mr. Oksalsa, and you won't be
drinking a lot. Since you're not
going to learn electronic shows by consent, I don't
think you'll avoid drinking Bokbunja wine because you're worried. I heard it
's good, but I'm curious. Would
moxibustion be okay, Mr. Oksalsa? I don't know much about moxibustion, like how
far away it is,
or anything like that.
But it's there.
Oxalate
can be inhaled as smoke.
In that sense, it would
n't be good to burn it and breathe in the smoke through your nose. We'll
wrap up the broadcast.
Nextweek,
next Saturday,
I think. Maybe Sunday?
If it's unclear when the meeting will end on Sunday, it's more
efficient.
No, we have to do gangpa on Saturday.
So, I
'll have to come on Sunday at 4 o'clock and turn on the broadcast.
Please submit it after leaving it for later and
press it again next week.
Thank you for watching.